Extending the Need for Performance Baselining
Hello, Mike Harry with you again, where we're going to explore the idea of baselines.
And how to establish those baselines. And why they're so critical.
to the operation of a business or a process.
You know, in order to gauge a relative speed. And the key word there is relative.
A relative speed, a relative performance, we need to benchmark that against some
stake in the ground. And that's a baseline.
Only then can we determine our rate of change, how fast we’re moving, etc.
It’s kind of our lighthouse, if you will. It's what we look back to
to determine our course, direction, and speed.
We’re going to get into this and come to understand baselines very well,
because it is so essential to the use of Six Sigma.
Thank you for choosing SSMI.